{
    "subject": "resource/The_Right_Stuff_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Aviation_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of The Right Stuff (film) is Aviation films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6164035201072693,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Aviation films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5768915414810181,
            "question": "Is 'The Right Stuff' a documentary or a fictional film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5476689338684082,
            "question": "How does 'The Right Stuff' portray the human experience of flight?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5467202067375183,
            "question": "What makes a film successful within the Aviation genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48473742604255676,
            "question": "Are there other films similar to 'The Right Stuff' in terms of genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4496360421180725,
            "question": "What genre does the film 'The Right Stuff' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34989452362060547,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors associated with 'The Right Stuff'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24581977725028992,
            "question": "What historical event might 'The Right Stuff' be based on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18127800524234772,
            "question": "Does 'The Right Stuff' focus on personal stories or larger historical events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1522882729768753,
            "question": "What impact did 'The Right Stuff' have on popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of The Right Stuff (film) is Aviation films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6836_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'The Right Stuff' focus on personal stories or larger historical events?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6836_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical event might 'The Right Stuff' be based on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6836_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors associated with 'The Right Stuff'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6836_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_161.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_163.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6836_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention that \"The movie captures the inherent danger of being a test pilot.\" and \"Before becoming astronauts, the Mercury Seven were pioneering test pilots, constantly putting their lives on the line as they pushed the limits of aviation technology.\" which suggests that the subject of The Right Stuff (film) is related to Aviation."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide ample evidence that \"The Right Stuff\" is indeed an aviation film, detailing its focus on the early days of the U.S. space program and test pilots, which falls under the broader category of aviation films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Right Stuff (film) primarily focuses on the early days of the U.S. space program, not aviation films per se. Although it does depict test pilots and their risky endeavors in the realm of aeronautical technology, its central theme revolves around the Mercury Seven astronauts and their monumental achievements in space exploration.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}